dontstayin.com 2015-12-30

# Privacy Policy - Don't Stay In

This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for Don't Stay In Ltd, a company incorporated in England & Wales with company number 08134054 and having its registered office at C/o Bacs 2 Basics Ltd, 15 Hillcrest Road, Blackburn, Lancashire, BB6 8EP. (“we”, “us”, “our” which shall also include subsidiary companies in which Web Giants Limited is the majority shareholder “Subsidiaries”). Our website is www.dontstayin.com  (the “Site”) and "the App" is any software we provide for use on electronic devices.

By accessing the Site or App and/or by submitting personal data manually or in electronic form to us in connection with the Site or App you give your consent that all personal data that you submit will be processed by us in the manner and for the purposes described below. 

Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it.

If you have any questions at all about this policy, the Site, the App or about how we use and process your personal information, please do not hesitate to contact us by e-mail at [ info@dontstayin.com](mailto:info@dontstayin.com) or, alternatively, in writing to: Don't Stay In Ltd C/o Bacs 2 Basics Ltd, 15 Hillcrest Road, Blackburn, Lancashire, BB6 8EP.

## Information Collection and Use

We are committed to protecting the privacy of the users of our Site or App. We are the sole owner of the information collected on the Site or App. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from those disclosed in this policy.

We may collect information from you at several different points on the Site or App, and may collect information from other companies, such as demographic and navigation data and information and data about you available from other websites or databases.

By submitting your information you consent to the use of that information as set out in this policy. If we change our privacy policy we will post the changes on this page, and may place notices on other pages of the Site, so that you may be aware of the information we collect and how we use it at all times. Continued use of the Site or App will constitute your agreement to any such changes.

The data we collect from you may be transferred to and stored in locations outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”).

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure and although we take all reasonable steps to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of it. Any transmission of personal data to the Site or App is at your own risk.

## Public (Unregistered) Users

We will not capture data about public (unregistered) users of the Site or App, other than your IP address and session details such as pages viewed and type of browser used. This information is automatically logged by the web server and will be used to evaluate the use and performance of the network.

## Offer Redemption

In order to redeem an offer via the Site or App, you must first complete the form and the details required in it. (During this process you are required to give your contact name and email address). This information is used to contact you about those services on the Site and App in which you have expressed an interest. It is optional for you to provide other demographic information, including that relating to your social networks which will enable us to access publicly available data, but this is encouraged so we can provide a more personalised experience of the Site and App.

## Social Media Connectivity

If you connect with us via Facebook and/or Twitter or similar social media application(s) then you consent to us posting your activity with us on your Facebook timeline and/or Twitter feed.  Each time you redeem an offer or save a venue or use the Site or App in other ways on the Site and/or App we will post this on the relevant social media application(s).  Please note that the default position will be to post your activity on your social media application(s).  If you have connected with us and do not wish for us to post your activity then you may disconnect the Site and App from your social media application(s) at any stage.  You will still be permitted to access offers and information on the Site and the App.

## Disclosures of your Information

We may disclose your information to third parties for the purposes set out below or where otherwise required or permitted by law to do so.

## Sharing

We may share (whether or not for payment) aggregated demographic information with our partners, clients and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. We may also use such aggregated information and statistics for monitoring the Site and App usage in order to help us develop the Site or Apps and our services and may provide such aggregated information to third parties for that purpose.

We may partner with another party to provide specific services. When you sign up for these services, we will share names or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personal information except for the purpose of providing these services.

We will share information between Don't Stay In Limited and the Subsidiaries.  This policy applies to all these companies.

## Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on your hard drive or device containing information about you. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on the Site. Once you close your browser, the cookie simply terminates. For instance, by setting a cookie on the Site, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on the Site. If you reject the cookie, you may not be able to use every function of the Site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target your interests to enhance your experience of the Site. Some of our business partners use cookies on this Site (for example, advertisers). We have no access to or control over these third party cookies.

By accepting this policy you are providing explicit consent to our use of cookies and to the presence of third party cookies on the Site. If you wish to opt out please adjust your web browser settings accordingly.

## Log Files

We use IP addresses to analyse trends, administer the Site and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

## Links

The Site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave the Site and to read the privacy policies of each and every website that collects personal information. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by us on the Site.

## Direct Mailings

We occasionally send out newsletters, information or alerts to our Site members and App users. We may also wish to provide you with information about special features of our Site or App or any other service or products we think may be of interest to you from us or from other parties. In relation to other parties this is an opt-in email option selected when you register your interest in the Site. At any time you can unsubscribe from further emails from about our services or those of third parties.

From time to time the Site will request information from you via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and address), and demographic information (such as postcode or age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use of and satisfaction with this site and mobile apps.

## Referrals by You

If you elect to use our referral service for informing a friend about our Site, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the Site. We store this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email. This information is then discarded after the email is sent.

## Data Protection Act 1998 (the “Act”)

We make every effort to ensure that our practices, procedures and systems comply with the relevant data protection legislation.

We will only use your personal data in accordance with the legal requirements and principles of the Act, which grants you various rights in respect of the processing of your personal data.

For more details about your rights under the Act, the rules we have to adhere to in collecting and storing your information, and how you can check your data records, please visit [www.ico.gov.uk](http://www.ico.gov.uk/).

You have a right to receive a copy of the information we hold about you by sending your request in writing, together with an administration fee of £15, to us at Don't Stay In Ltd C/o Bacs 2 Basics Ltd, 15 Hillcrest Road, Blackburn, Lancashire, BB6 8EP.

## Updating/Removal of Personal Information

If any information regarding you requires to be corrected, updated or changed it is your responsibility to advise us of the required amendments.

If you inform us that you no longer desire our service, we shall correct, update or remove your personal data provided to us. An archive copy of any information provided to us may be retained by us for our records, for use in statistical analysis and for audit purposes and will not be used for other purposes.

## Contact

If you have any questions at all about this policy, the Site or Apps or about how we use and process your personal information, please do not hesitate to contact us at us by e-mail at [info@dontstayin.com](mailto:info@dontstayin.com) or, alternatively, in writing to Don't Stay In Ltd C/o Bacs 2 Basics Ltd, 15 Hillcrest Road, Blackburn, Lancashire, BB6 8EP.
